# **SERGEI DOCHKIN**

+375 55 44-94-67 | SERGEYSHARK@GMAIL.COM | LINKEDIN.COM/IN/SDOCHKIN | YEREVAN, ARMENIA

#### **SUMMARY**

Frontend developer with over 6 years of expirience, currently working and living in Yerevan. I'm developing towards backend, I plan to grow into a teamleader.

I like working with people, I enjoy taking on communication with colleagues, mentoring and leadership in certain issues. I have worked in big fintech companies, and I know what it means to implement scrum and work out a project from scratch.

I like to take active part in development, build processes, mentoring. I like studying English, algorithms and backend development, and all sorts of self-development.

I want to be able to influence the processes inside the team, not just write tons of code.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Voronezh State Technical University**

Voronezh, Russia

Specialist degree, Information technology in education

Sep. 2010 – July 2015

# **EXPERIENCE**

# JavaScript Teacher

July 2022 - Present

**Elbrus Coding Bootcamp** 

Moscow, Russia

• In almost a year of teaching, I graduated four groups of students (about 80 people), 90% of whom found a job after graduation.

# **Senior Frontend Developer**

Jan. 2022 - July 2022

Mission:Luna

Moscow, Russia

• Acted as a liaison, using communication skills to remove bottlenecks in interactions between teams. As a result, I accelerated our decision-making processes and product cycle by about 30%.

## **Senior Frontend Developer**

Oct. 2021 - Dec. 2021

Infourok

Moscow, Russia

• Participated in the development of the project roadmap, began to implement the project logging and analytics of user actions. Left due to downsizing.

## **Senior Frontend Developer**

June 2020 - Oct. 2021

VTB Bank

Moscow, Russia

• Supported three projects simultaneously. Introduced into the codebase a gathering of custom metrics, increased test coverage from 83% to 92%.

## **Frontend Developer**

Oct. 2019 - July 2020

Sberbank

Moscow, Russia

• Coming to the project as the only junior developer, in 10 months: implemented Scrum, cleaned up the code base of several projects, and developed one project from scratch to release. Trained one intern.

## **Junior Frontend Developer**

July 2018 - Oct. 2019

Neoflex

Voronezh, Russia

• UI-Kit development for internal projects, credit pipeline development for VTB Bank, code support and maintenance, code coverage by tests, bug fixing.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, NodeJS, Express, SQL (Postgres), HTML/CSS, GraphQL, Redux-Thunk, Redux-Saga, Jest, Git

## LANGUAGES

Russian: Native English: Intermediate